Guide to the Larry L. King Papers
The Wittliff Collections
- Correspondence, 1957-1993
  Correspondence forms the bulk of the King Papers, filling over 21 boxes. It is arranged chronologically, reflecting King's own arrangement -- he kept a box under his desk where he tosses the letters (with a copy of his response attached) as he answers them. When the box becomes full, King stuffs the letters into a large brown envelope upon which he marks the months and year covered.
  The correspondence describes writing projects, including fan response and King's reaction to it. He is generous with advice to aspiring writers and frequently discusses the literary craft with his writer friends. Writer correspondents include Borden Deal, Ronnie Dugger, Peter Gent, A. C. Greene, Norman Mailer, Jay Milner, Willie Morris, Terry Pringle, Frank Rich, Edwin (Bud) Shrake, H. Allen Smith, William Styron, Barlow Herget, and, less frequently, Billy Lee Brammer, Jim Brosnan, Jim Lehrer, Larry McMurtry, Bill Moyers and Bill Wittliff. Other correspondents are the Texas attorney, Warren Burnett, King's cousin Lanvil Gilbert, legislator and The Kingfish co-writer Ben Z. Grant, Midland lawyer Reagan Legg, Director Keith Kennedy, high school coach Aubra Nooncaster, politicians Morris Udall and Jim Wright, and many more friends and family.
  - 1957-1964 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - 1965-1971 [No Month] (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - 1965 [No Month] (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - January - August 1965 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - September - December 1965 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - January - February 1966 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - March - April 1966 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - May 1966 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - June 1966 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - July 1966 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - August 1966 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - September - October 1966 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - November - December 1966 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - January - February 1967 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - March - April 1967 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - May - June 1967 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - July 1967 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - August 1967 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - September - November 1967 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - December 1967 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - January - February 1968 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - March - April 1968 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - May 1968 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - June 1968 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - July 1968 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - August 1968 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - September 1968 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - October 1968 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - November 1968 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - December 1968 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - January 1969 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - February 1969 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - March 1969 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - April 1969 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - May 1969 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - June 1969 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - July 1969 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - August 1969 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - September 1969 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - October 1969 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - November 1969 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - December 1969 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - 1970 [No Month] (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - January 1970 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - February - March 1970 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - April – June 1970 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - July 1970 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - August 1970 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - September 1970 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - October 1970 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - November 1970 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - December 1970 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - 1971 [No Month} (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - January-February 1971 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - March 1971 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - April 1971 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - May 1971 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - June 1971 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - July - August 1971 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - September - October 1971 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - November 1971 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - December 1971 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - 1972 [No Month] (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - January 1972 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - February 1972 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - March 1972 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - April - May 1972 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - June 1972 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - July - August 1972 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - September - October 1972 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - November - December 1972 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - 1973 [No Month] (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - January - February 1973 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - March - April 1973 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - May - June 1973 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - July - September 1973 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - October - November 1973 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - December 1973 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - 1974 [No Month] (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - January 1974 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - February 1974 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - March 1974 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - April - June 1974 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - July - September 1974 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - October - November 1974 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - December 1974 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - 1975 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - January 1977 - March 1980 (Box 27)
  - April 1980 - July 1981 (Box 28)
  - August 1981 - December 1982 (Box 29)
  - January 1983 - March 1984 (Box 30)
  - April 1984 - July 1985 (Box 31)
  - August 1985 - August 1986 (Box 32)
  - September 1986 - October 1987 (Box 33)
  - November 1987 - July 1988 (Box 34)
  - August 1988 - April 1989 (Box 35)
  - May 1989 - December 1989 (Box 36)
  - January 1990 – September 1990 (Box 37)
  - October 1990 – November 1991 (Box 38)
  - December 1991 – March 1993 (Box 39)